<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bequest</string>
    <string name="entrance">This is the main entrance to the golconda fort.Mythical beasts and lions on stucco panels of the spandrels provide decoration on this defence portal. Upon entering the fort through Balahissar gate, We can see mortuary bath on right, Aslah Khana on left and a connon infront while standing below a dome. A clap below the dome at a particular spot can be heard from Durbar hall located a few hundred meters away at the top of the hill. Whenever visitors arrived at the gate, a man stationed here would communicate it to the Sultan’s guards atop the hill—by clapping. Codes were used: one clap for a friend, two for a foe (in which case, the gates along the outer walls would be shut at once, three for an honoured guest, and so on</string>
    <string name="clap">A clap below the dome at a particular spot can be heard from Durbar hall located a few hundred meters away at the top of the hill. Whenever visitors arrived at the gate, a man stationed here would communicate it to the Sultan’s guards atop the hill—by clapping. Codes were used: one clap for a friend, two for a foe (in which case, the gates along the outer walls would be shut at once, three for an honoured guest, and so on</string>
    <string name="mortuary">The mortuary baths lie to the right of the Clapping portico. The baths were meant for the deceased royalty and harem ladies(wives and concubines) who were given the ritualistic bath before burial outside the Banjara Gate</string>
    <string name="guest">This is where the royal guests used to stay</string>
    <string name="garden">Nagina Bagh which means “Jewel among the Gardens”. It was designed after the typical Mughal Gardens and has a square layout divided into quadrants by paved pathways converging into a fountain located at the centre of the gardens.This is where the diamond trade used to take place. There is also a mosque that was built for the use of diamond merchants coming to trade in the Nagina Bagh</string>
    <string name="ramdas">This is where Kancherla Goppana(Ramdas) was imprisoned by the Sultan for embezzling Royal funds to build a temple for a Hindhu God Ram at Bhadrachalam. Food was provided to him from the entries in the ceiling. During his imprisonment Ramdas painted the Hindhu Gods Ram along with others on the walls of the prison</string>
    <string name="granary">The Ambar Khana_royal granary) has a Persian inscription on black basalt stating that it was built by Khairat Khan between 1626 and 1672 during the reign of Abdullah Qutb Shah. This was the granary storage for the fort</string>
    <string name="ibrahim">This mosque was built by Ibrahim Qutub Shah which is distinguished by the prominent corner minarets. This mosque was built on top of Ambar Khana. The courtyard of the mosque extends up to the ramparts providing magnificent views of the landscape below.Ibrahim Mosque is a good example of Qutb Shahi architecture. This simple yet beautiful mosque is marked by three arches with the central being larger than the flanking smaller arches on it’s either sides. At the base it has nine small arches. The external stucco decorations represent typical Qutb Shahi art style</string>
    <string name="temple">This is a Hindu temple of Madanna, which belongs to the Kakatiya period. It is carved out of a huge boulder and has colorful frescos of the Goddess Kali on the white-painted facade</string>
    <string name="baradari">At the summit of the hill is the three-storeyed breezy Durbar Hall(“Throne Room”), with a rooftop pavilion. Also known as Baradari, this is the highest point in the fort. This is a double-storeyed structure, the lower storey functioning as the Diwan-e-Aam(the Hall of Public Audience), the upper as the Diwan-e-Khaas(the Hall of Private Audience). From here, the Sultan used catch a view of entire city of Hyderabad. At a particular location in this Durbar Hall, one can hear the clapping sound produced at Balahissar Darwaza</string>
    <string name="view">From here there are wonderful views of the entire fort and its surroundings, which include two pretty structures on hillocks – Taramati Baradari and Premamati’s Mosque. These are named after the two dancers who were royal favourites, and said to be so lightfooted that they could dance all the way from the pavilion to the Bala Hisar on a tightrope</string>
    <string name="secreteriat">This is where the famous Akkanna and Madanna brothers used to have their offices. This place was later used by many clerks and lower officials serving the fort as their offices to maintain fort records</string>
    <string name="armoury">Also called as Silah Khana, This place is used as armoury during Qutub Shahi times. It is said to have around 150 rooms. Some of the long cannons with few cannon balls are displayed in one of the large arched windows here. Since Silah Khana is essential to fort defences, it is situated close to Balahissar gate</string>
    <string name="drums">This is where the Drum bearers used to perform during festivals and ceremonies</string>
    <string name="taramati">A small mosque dedicated for the dancer and queen Taramati</string>
    <string name="bhagmati"></string>
    <string name="court">Sultan used to hear grievances of the people and pass judgements on criminals at this place. The hall has been designed in such a way that even a whisper at one end of the hall can be heard from the other end of the room. Sultan used to sit on the balcony overseeing the proceedings. This hall is also known as Hall of Justice</string>
    <string name="rani">The queen of Sultan used to stay here. The walls are covered with decorative niches, alcoves and cornices, inspired by Persian design</string>
    <string name="kilwat">This is a small two storied chamber specially designed to be the Royal private quarters</string>
    <string name="zenanaDressingRoom">This place was used as dressing room by the women in Zenana. This dressing room was also used by famous dancers Taramati and Premamati who were married to Sultan</string>
    <string name="zenanaMosque">A prayer place for the Royal women and other women staying in womens area, the Zenana</string>
    <string name="zenanaBodyguards">This is where the women bodyguards of the Zenana used to have quarters</string>
    <string name="camel">This is where camels were kept</string>
    <string name="dhobi">All the clothes of the royal family used to be washed here</string>
    <string name="whisper">This room was used by the royal ladies to entertain guests. The Sultan, to keep tabs on what was discussed, could even listen in on private conversations because the walls were designed to amplify sound</string>
</resources>
